ujam.com 2019-04-11

# Privacy Policy EN - ujam Shop

of

NXTGN Music Technology GmbH

An der Reeperbahn 6

28217 Bremen

Deutschland

## 1 GENRAL

We take the protection and security of your personal data very seriously and collect, process, store and use your personal data - finally within the framework of the provisions of the European basic data protection regulations (GDPR) as well as the data protection laws in the Federal Republic of Germany. 

In order for you to have the best possible control over your data, we inform you with our privacy policy which personal data we collect when you use our website "ujam.com" (hereinafter "website"), how we use this data and what rights and scope for design you have. 

Personal data are all information relating to identified or identifiable natural person, e.g. first name, surname, email address. 

## 2 COLLECTION,PROCESSING,STORAGEANDUSEOFYOURDATA

### 2.1 COLLECTION, PROCESSING, STORAGE AND USE OF YOUR DATA WHEN USING OUR WEBSITE

#### 2.1.1 LOG DATA WHEN YOU VISIT OUR WEBSITE

Our website is available to everyone without prior registration at at your disposal. Your internet browser or your mobile device automatically sends the following data to our web server when accessing our website from technical reasons: 

  * IP address of your device, 
  * Date and time of access, 
  * URL of the requesting website, 
  * http response code, 
  * Name of the retrieved file, 
  * the amount of data sent, 
  * browser type and version, and 
  * Operating system of your device. 

This data is stored by our web server in log files. This data is not stored together with other personal data. 

The legal basis für the storage of this data is Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f GDPR. 

This data is used by us to analyse the use of our website and its technical administration, the security of our information technology systems , errors, to prevent misuse of our website and to optimise our website. These purposes are the legitimate interests pursued by us with the data processing gemäß Art. 6 Par. 1 lit. f GDPR. 

The data will be used by us and deleted as soon as they are no longer required to achieve the purpose of their collection. In the case of saving the data in log files, the data is stored for seven days and will be deleted after this time span. A storage beyond of the log data is possible, if the IP address of your device is alienated or in such a way that an assignment of the IP address to you is no longer possible. 

#### 2.1.2 COOKIES

Our website uses cookies. Cookies are small files that are stored on the hard disk of the device. They will uniquely identify your computer system when you visit our website again at the request of our web server. 

We use cookies to make the use of our website more comfortable for you, e.g. through the user-defined possibilities, to store login data (technically necessary cookies). We also use cookies to analyse your use of our website (technically unnecessary cookies). 

When you visit our website, an info banner informs you of the use of technically unnecessary cookies for analysis purposes and points you to this privacy policy. In this context, we also obtain your consent to the processing of your personal data 

The legal basis for the processing of your data using cookies is Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f GDPR. If you have given your consent, the legal basis is the processing of your data in addition Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR. 

Technically necessary cookies are used by us to simplify the use of our website für you. Some functions of our website are not offered and used without the use of technically necessary cookies. Cookies that are not technically necessary are used by us to design and constantly optimize our website. These purposes are the legitimate interests according to Art. 6 Par. 1 lit. f GDPR, which are followed by us with the data processing. 

Cookies are automatically accepted by most browsers or operating systems. If you do not use this, you should configure your browser to prevent cookies from being set (deactivation). Cookies already stored can also be stored at any time. Please note that by deactivating the functional scope of our websites may be possible, so that you may not use all functions of our websites. 

You can revoke your consent to this future at any time by contacting us. By revoking your consent, the legality of the processing of your data on the basis of your consent until revocation under use of cookies does not. Please note that by refusing or revoking your consent, the functionality of our website may become available, so that you may not use all the features of our website. 

### 2.2 COLLECTION, PROCESSING, STORAGE AND USE OF YOUR DATA FOR ORDERS AT OUR ONLINESHOP

#### 2.2.1 ORDERS AT OUR ONLINESHOP

An order at our online shop is possible after prior registration with the obligatory data (registration data). 

Email address and password 

as well as a shipping address and your payment data. In addition to the mandatory data you may provide further data voluntarily. 

The legal basis for the processing of your registration, dispatch and payment data is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. b GDPR. 

We use the data for the completion of your order, the production and administration of your user account, the supply of the ordered goods and/or the rendering of the agreed services, for the completion of the payment as well as for the establishment of contact. 

Your registration data as well as the shipping and payment data will be deleted when you delete your user account. If your data is required for the fulfilment of a contract of which you are a party or for pre-contractual measures, the data will only become deleted when it is no longer necessary for the fulfilment of the contract or the pre-contractual measures. However, we would like to point out that it may also be necessary to store your data in accordance with fulfilment of the contract in order to comply with contractual or legal obligations. 

#### 2.2.2 LOG DATA FOR ORDERS AT OUR ONLINESHOP

When you access our website, the data accordingly to 2.1. of this privacy policy is also collected and stored automatically. 

### 2.3 PROCESSING OF CREDIT CARD DATA

Credit card data are exclusively transmitted over a TLS-encrypted connection to the Web Payment Frontend of the company PAYONE GmbH, where the correctness of the card data is compared with the respective credit card institute and credit rating. NXTGN does not store your credit card information. 

### 2.4 ORDER PROCESSING WITH PAYPAL

In order to process your payment with the company PayPal, Inc, by a TLS- encrypted link, personal data (name and address) will be forwarded to Paypal. 

### 2.5 COLLECTION, PROCESSING, STORAGE AND USE OF YOUR DATA WHEN USING THE AREA OF OUR WEBSITE SUBJECT TO REGISTRATION

#### 2.5.1 LOGIN

When you purchase the SOFTWARE LICENSE, you must register on our website with the required data (registration data). 

Email address and password 

to register the software purchased from us once. After entering your registration data, this data is stored together with a license key and a digital fingerprint of your hardware configuration in the registration database of NXTGN. To use the licensed SOFTWARE, after purchasing a SOFTWARE LICENSE, the SOFTWARE must be authorised in an online process in order to use it. 

In addition to the mandatory data you can provide further data voluntarily. As part of the registration process, we collect your consent to the processing of your registration data and other data. 

The legal basis for the processing of your registration data and other data is, with your consent, Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR. If the registration of fulfilment serves the purpose of a contract of which you are a contracting party or of pre- contractual measures, then the legal basis is the processing of your registration data as well as the further data in addition to Art. 6 para. 1 lit. b GDPR. 

We use the registration data für the reason and handling of the usage of the area of our website requiring registration, in particular for your unique identification, for the creation and administration of your user account, for the authorization of the licensed software as well as for contacting. 

If the registration of fulfilment serves a contract of which you are a contracting party, or the fulfilment of pre-contractual measures, we will also use your data for the reason and handling of contractual and any pre-contractual measures. Your registration data as well as further data will be deleted if you make a corresponding request by e-mail to support@ujam.com. Afterwards your request for deletion will be confirmed and fulfilled. If your registration data and other data are required for fulfilment of a contract to which you are a contracting party or for fulfilling pre-contractual measures, the data will only become deleted when they are no longer required for the fulfilment of the contract or the fulfilment of pre-contractual measures. However, we would like to point out that it may be necessary to store your registration data even after fulfilment of the contract in order to comply with contractual or legal obligations. 

You can revoke your consent to the processing of your registration data and other data at any time with immediate effect and will be revoked the future. The legality of the processing of your registration data based on your consent until revocation will not be touched. If your registration data is required for the fulfilment of a contract or for fulfilling pre-contractual measures, a (premature) deletion of your data is only possible, as far as contractual or legal obligations do not conflict with a deletion. 

#### 2.5.2 LOG DATA WHEN USING THE AREA OF OUR WEBSITE THAT REQUIRES REGISTRATION

When you access our website, the data according to 2.1. of this privacy policy is also collected and stored automatically. 

### 2.6 COLLECTION, PROCESSING, STORAGE AND USE OF YOUR DATA TO THE RECEIPT OF OUR NEWSLETTER

#### 2.6.1 NEWSLETTER REGISTRATION

You have the possibility, under indication of your email address, to subscribe to our free newsletter at our website. After entering your email address you will receive an email from us to the email address you provided. By clicking on the included link, you confirm that you authorized to access the given email address (so-called double opt-in procedure) and activate the newsletter reception. When you register to receive our newsletter, we collect your consent to the processing of your data. 

The legal basis for the processing of your data after registration for our newsletter is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. a GDPR. 

We will only use the email address you provided to send you our newsletter. 

The email address you provide will only be stored by us for as long as you wish to receive our newsletter. You can revoke your given consent at any time and unsubscribe with immediate effect. You may also revoke your consent by clicking on the unsubscribe link contained in the footer of each newsletter. By revoking your consent, your consent will not accept the receipt of the newsletter due to your consent until revoked processing of your data. 

#### 2.6.2 LOG DATA FOR NEWSLETTER REGISTRATION

When you access our web pages, the data accordingly Section 2.1. of this privacy policy is also collected and stored automatically. 

### 2.7 COLLECTION, PROCESSING, STORAGE AND USE OF YOUR DATA UPON CONTACT

#### 2.7.1 CONTACTING BY EMAIL

You have got the possibility to contact us, via our e-mail address 

info@ujam.com. 

In this case, your personal data will be stored by us by the transmitted e-mail. 

The legal basis for the processing of your personal data, which you send us in the context of electronic contact by e-mail, is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f GDPR. If the electronic contact via email is aimed at the conclusion of a contract with us, the legal basis for this is the processing of your personal data in addition Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. GDPR. 

We use your data to process your request and to contact you. These purposes are the legitimate interests pursued by us with the data processing according to Art. 6 Par. 1 lit. f GDPR. Your data will - insofar as there are no contractual or legal obligations to the contrary - be used by us as soon as it is no longer necessary for us to achieve the above-mentioned purposes; this is the case if the subject matter of your electronic contact is completely clarified. If you conclude a contract with us on the basis of your electronic contact, your data will only become deleted when they are no longer required for the fulfilment of the contract or the through fulfilling pre-contractual measures. We would like to point this out, that it may be necessary to store your data even after fulfilling of the contract in order to comply with contractual or legal obligations. 

Ihre Daten werden – soweit nicht vertragliche oder gesetzliche Verpflichtungen einer Löschung entgegenstehen – von uns gelöscht, sobald sie für die Erreichung der vorgenannten Zwecke nicht mehr erforderlich sind; dies ist der Fall, wenn der Ihrer elektronischen Kontaktaufnahme zugrundeliegende Sachverhalt vollständig geklärt ist. Wenn Sie aufgrund Ihrer elektronischen Kontaktaufnahme einen Vertrag mit uns schließen, werden Ihre Daten erst dann gelöscht, wenn sie für die Erfüllung des Vertrages oder die Durchführung vorvertraglicher Maßnahmen nicht mehr erforderlich sind. Wir weisen darauf hin, dass eine Erforderlichkeit, Ihre Daten zu speichern, auch nach Erfüllung des Vertrages bestehen kann, um vertraglichen oder gesetzlichen Verpflichtungen nachzukommen. 

You can object to the use of your personal data at any time without creating any other than transmission costs. In such a case, your data stored in the context of electronic contact will be deleted; the processing of your request cannot be fulfilled If your data is required for the fulfilment of a contract or for fulfilling pre-contractual measures, a (premature) deletion of your data is only possible, as far as contractual or legal obligations of deletion do not conflict. 

#### 2.7.2 SUPPORT BY EMAIL

You have got the possibility to contact us for support purposes, via our e-mail address 

support@ujam.com. 

In this case, your personal data will be stored by us. 

The legal basis für is the processing of your personal data, which you send us in the context of electronic contact by e-mail, is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f GDPR. If the electronic contact via e-mail is aimed at a purchase or a contractual service with us, the legal basis for this is the processing of your personal data in addition Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. b GDPR. 

We use your data to process your support request. These purposes are the legitimate interests pursued by us with the data processing according to Art. 6 Par. 1 lit. f GDPR. We use the helpdesk tool of Zendesk, 1019 Market St., San Francisco, CA 94103 to support management. For information on terms of use and privacy, see: 

https://www.zendesk.com/company/policies-procedures/ 

Your data will - insofar as there are no contractual or legal obligations to the contrary - be deleted by us as soon as it is no longer necessary for us to achieve the above-mentioned purposes; this is the case if the subject matter of your electronic contact is completely clarified. If you conclude a contract with us on the basis of your electronic contact, your data for the fulfilment of the contract or the fulfilment of pre-contractual measures are no longer necessary and they will be deleted. We would like to point out that it may also be necessary to store your data after fulfilment of the contract in order to comply with contractual or legal obligations. 

You can object to the use of your personal data at any time without creating any other than transmission costs. In such a case, your data stored in the context of electronic contact will be deleted; the processing of your request cannot be pursued. If your data is required for the fulfilment of a contract or for fulfilling pre-contractual measures, a (premature) deletion of your data is only possible, as far as contractual or legal obligations of deletion do not conflict. 

#### 2.7.3 CONTACT LOG DATA

When you access our website, the data according to 2.1. of this privacy policy is also collected and stored automatically. 

### 2.8 COLLECTION, PROCESSING, STORAGE AND USE OF YOUR DATA FOR (UNSOLICITED) APPLICATIONS BY EMAIL

#### 2.8.1 (UNSOLICITED) APPLICATION BY EMAIL

You have got the possibility to a job advertisement or to send us an unsolicited application, via our e-mail address 

info@ujam.com. 

In this case, your personal data transferred to us will be stored by us. 

The legal basis for the processing of your personal data, which you send us in the context of your (unsolicited) application by email, is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f GDPR. Your (unsolicited) application by email to justify a job with us, is the legal basis für the processing of your personal data furthermore art. 6 para. 1 lit.b GDPR as well as § 26 para. 1 GDPR (new). We use your personal data for the fulfilment of the application process, for inspection and processing of your (unsolicited) application, for the decision of a employment with us as well as for answering your inquiries and for establishing contact. These purposes are the legitimate interests pursued by us with the data processing according to Art. 6 Par. 1 lit. f GDPR. 

Your data will - insofar as there are no contractual or legal obligations to the contrary - be used by us 6 months after completion of the application process, If you conclude a contract with us on the basis of your (unsolicited)application, your data will only become deleted when it is no longer necessary for the fulfilment of the contract or pre-contractual measures. We point out that it may be necessary to store your personal data even after termination of the contract in order to comply with contractual or legal obligations. 

You can object to using your personal data at any time without creating any other than transmission costs. In such a case, your data stored in the context of your (unsolicited) application will be deleted; the processing of your (unsolicited) application cannot become pursued. If your data is required for fulfilling a contract or pre-contractual measures, a (premature) deletion of your data is only possible, as far as contractual or legal obligations of a deletion stand in the way. 

#### 2.8.2 LOG DATA FOR (UNSOLICITED) APPLICATIONS BY EMAIL

When you access our website, the data according to 2.1. of this privacy policy is also collected and stored automatically. 

#### 3 FORWARDING OF PERSONAL DATA

A passing on, a sale or another transmission of your personal data to third parties does not take place, unless this is necessary for the purpose of the fulfilment of a contract. Otherwise, we will only pass on your personal data to third parties within the framework of a legal permission or on the basis of your revocable consent at any time and only to the extent that is necessary for the fulfilment of our contractual obligations. 

Our service partners (e.g. hosting service providers) require your personal data and process them exclusively on our behalf in the context of an order processing, which is explicitly provided by Art. 28 para. 3 GDPR. 

We will only disclose your personal data to government agencies or public authorities if we are required to do so by law. 

### 3.1 INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM OTHER SOURCES

To offer you prize raffles or exclusive content, we work closely with third parties (for example, advertising networks) and may receive information, including Personal Data, about you from them. This could include socio-demographic information. We may combine this information with other information you have provided to us or which we collected about you. 

## 4 EVALUATION OF USAGE BEHAVIOR

### 4.1 GOOGLE ANALYTICS

We use the services of Google Analytics, a web analysis service of Google Inc, 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA ("Google"). 

Google Analytics uses tracking code and "cookies", small text files that are stored on the device you are using, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie of our website is usually stored on a Google server in the USA. However, due to the activation of IP anonymisation "anonymizeIp", your IP address will previously be used by Google within member states of the European Union or in other contracting states of the agreement über the European economic area. The IP address used in the context of Google Analytics by your browser will not be matched with other data from Google. 

The legal basis für the processing of your data is Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f GDPR. If you have given your consent, the legal basis is the processing of your data in addition Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR. We use Google's web analysis service to design, constantly improve and optimize our website to meet your needs. On our behalf, Google uses the data and information collected to evaluate your use of our website, to compile reports, website activities and to provide other services relating to the use of our website and the Internet. These purposes are the legitimate interests pursued by us with the data processing gemäß Art. 6 Par. 1 lit. f GDPR. 

If you choose to refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the functions of our website entirely. You can also prevent Google from collecting the data generated by the cookie and relating to your use of our website (including your IP address) and from processing this data by Google by downloading and installing the browser plug-in under the following link: 

http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de 

Further information on terms of use and data protection can be found at: 

http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/de.html und https://www.google.de/intl/de/policies/. 

Your consent to the processing of your data can be revoked at any time with immediate effect. However, by revoking your consent, we will not process your data on the basis of your consent until revocation. Please note that by revoking your consent, the functionality of our website may become limited available, so that you may not use all the functions of our website. 

###  4.2 GOOGLE ADWORDS CONVERSION TRACKING 

We also use Google Adwords Conversion Tracking, a web analysis service of Google Inc, 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA ("Google"). 

Google Adwords uses tracking code and "cookies", small text files that are stored on the device you use, provided that you have reached via a Google ad on our website. The cookie loses its validation after 30 days. If you visit our website again within these 30 days, Google may recognize that you clicked on a Google ad and were redirected to our website. 

The legal basis for the processing of your data is Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f GDPR. If you have given your consent, the legal basis for this is the processing of your data in addition Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR. 

We use Google's web analysis service to statistically record the use of our website and to continuously improve and optimise our website. On our behalf, Google uses the data and information collected to evaluate your use of our website and to create reports (so-called conversion statistics) for us. The conversion statistics tell us how many users clicked on our ad and were redirected to our website with a conversion tracking tag. These purposes are the legitimate interests pursued by us with the data processing according to Art. 6 Par. 1 lit. f GDPR. 

If you choose to refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, please be aware that if you do this you may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. You will possibly not be able to use our website fully. 

Further information on data protection can be found at: 

https://services.google.com/sitestats/de.html 

Your consent to the processing of your data and can be refused at any time with immediate effect. However, by revoking your consent, we will not process your data on the basis of your consent until revocation. Please note that by revoking your consent, the functionality of our website may become limited available, so that you may not use all the functions of our website. 

###  4.3 FACEBOOK CONVERSION TRACKING 

Our website includes so-called social media plugins ("plugins") of the social network Facebook. Facebook is operated by Facebook Inc, 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA ("Facebook"). An overview of the plugins of Facebook and their appearance can be found here: 

When you visit our website and activate the plugin, the plugin establishes a direct connection between your browser and the Facebook server. Facebook provides the information that you have accessed our website with your browser, even if you do not have a Facebook profile or are not currently logged in. This information (including your IP address) is stored by your browser directly on a Facebook server in the USA. If you are logged in to Facebook, Facebook can immediately associate your visit to our website with your profile on Facebook. The information are also displayed on the social network and your contacts there. 

The purpose and scope of data collection and the further processing and use of the data by Facebook as well as your rights and preferences for the protection of your privacy can be found in the data protection information of Facebook under: 

http://www.facebook.com/policy.php 

You can deactivate the facebook conversion tracking by clicking the following link. 

## 5 SOCIAL MEDIA PLUGINS

Social Media Plugins ("Plugins") of the social networks Facebook, the microblogging service Twitter and the video portal YouTube ("provider") are integrated on our website on the basis of art. 6 par. 1 lit. f GDPR. 

###  5.1 FACEBOOK

Our website includes so-called social media plugins ("plugins") of the social network Facebook. Facebook is operated by Facebook Inc, 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA ("Facebook"). An overview of the plugins of Facebook and their appearance can be found here: 

https://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins 

When you visit our website and activate the plugin, the plugin establishes a direct connection between your browser and the Facebook server. Facebook provides the information that you have accessed our website with your browser, even if you do not have a Facebook profile or are not currently logged in. This information (including your IP address) is stored by your browser directly on a Facebook server in the USA. If you are logged in to Facebook, Facebook can immediately associate your visit to our website with your profile on Facebook. If you interact with the plugin, for example the “Like” button, the corresponding information is also saved directly to a Facebook server. The information are also displayed on the social network and your contacts there. 

The purpose and scope of data collection and the further processing and use of the data by Facebook as well as your rights and preferences for the protection of your privacy can be found in the data protection information of Facebook under: 

http://www.facebook.com/policy.php 

If you do not wish that Facebook can associate the visit to our website with your Facebook account, please log out of your Facebook account. 

### 5.2 TWITTER

Our website includes so-called social media plugins ("plugins") of the microblogging service Twitter. Twitter is operated by Twitter Inc, 1355 Market St, Suite 900, San Francisco, CA 94103, USA ("Twitter"). An overview of the Twitter buttons and their appearance can be found here: 

https://twitter.com/about/resources/buttons 

When you visit our website and activate the plugin, the plugin establishes a direct connection between your browser and the Twitter server. By integrating the plugin Twitter receives the information that your browser has called our website, even if you do not have a Twitter profile or are not currently logged in. This information (including your IP address) is stored by your browser directly on a Twitter server in the USA. If you interact with the plugin, for example the "Twitter"-button, the corresponding information is sent directly to a server of Twitter and stored there. The information is also displayed on your Twitter account and your contacts there. 

The purpose and scope of data collection and the further processing and use of your data by Twitter as well as your rights and preferences for the protection of your privacy can be found in the Twitter data protection information at: 

https://twitter.com/privacy 

If you do not wish that Twitter associates the data collected at our website with your Twitter profile, please log out of your Twitter account. 

###  5.3 YOU TUBE

Our website also includes so-called social media plugins ("plugins") of the video portal YouTube. YouTube is operated by YouTube LLC, 901 Cherry Ave, San Bruno, CA 94066, USA ("YouTube"). 

When you visit our website and activate the plugin, the plugin establishes a direct connection between your browser and the YouTube server. YouTube receives the information that you have accessed our website with your browser, even if you do not have a YouTube account or are not currently logged in. This information (including your IP address) is stored by your browser directly on a YouTube server in the USA. If you are logged in to YouTube, YouTube can immediately associate your visit to our website with your YouTube account. 

Further information on YouTube's collection and use of your data, your rights and preferences to protect your privacy can be found in YouTube's privacy policy at: 

https://www.google.de/intl/de/policies/privacy 

If you do not wish that YouTube associates the collected information directly with your YouTube account, please log out before visiting our website at YouTube. 

## 6 RESPONSIBLE OFFICE

Responsible for the processing of your personal data is: 

NXTGN Music Technology GmbH 

An der Reeperbahn 6 

28217 Bremen 

Deutschland 

Tel: +49 421 898 097 00 

Fax: +49 421 898 097 09 

info@ujam.com 

## 7 DATA PROTECTION OFFICER

We have ordered 

Mr Günther Ewald 

HEC GmbH 

Konsul-Smidt-Straße 20 

28217 Bremen 

Telefon: +49 421 / 20750-0 

Email: datenschutz@neusta.de 

as our data protection officer. 

## 8 LOCATION OF YOUR DATA / DATA SECURITY

Our servers and data centers are owned by Amazon Web Services, Inc. and processed by Amazon Web Services, Inc. 

As a rule, we process your personal data within the European Union. However, we also use the services of some third-party providers. If these third parties are in areas in which no level of data protection complies with the regulations applicable within the European Union, we will take all necessary steps to ensure that your personal data are appropriately secured. We achieve this either by concluding data protection contracts or by making sure that the third party providers are certified according to suitable security standards (e.g. the EU-US data protection shield (EU-US Privacy Shield)). 

We take various physical, technical, organizational and administrative security measures to adequately protect your data depending on the sensibility of the data to be secured. 

We use an SSL-encryption on our website, in particular to protect your personal data. You can recognize the encrypted connection by the lock symbol in the address line of your browser. 

## 9 YOUR RIGHTS

### 9.1 RIGHT TO INFORMATION

You are entitled to request information from us free of charge at any time as to whether we are processing personal data relating to you. If this is the case, you have a right of access to these personal data as well as to information for processing. 

For the protection of your data we reserve the right to request a identity check. 

We provide you with information on data protection law in a reasonable electronic format. 

### 9.2 RIGHT TO CORRECTION

You also have the right to request us to correct any inaccurate personal data. Furthermore, you have the right - at consideration for the purposes of processing your personal data - to request completion of incomplete personal data from us. 

### 9.3 RIGHT TO LIMITATION OF PROCESSING

You have the right, under certain conditions, to request us to limit the process of your personal data. 

If the processing of your personal data is limited, apart from their storage, these data will only be processed with your consent or to make it valid, exercise or to defend legal claims or to protect the rights of another natural or legal person or from reasons in an important public interest of the Union or a Member State. 

If you have obtained a limitation of the processing of your personal data, you will be informed by us before the limitation is revoked. 

### 9.4 RIGHT ON DELETION ("RIGHT TO BE FORGOTTEN")

You have the right, under certain conditions, to request immediate deletion of your personal information. 

The right to deletion of your personal data does not exist, as far as the processing is necessary. 

  * to exercise of the right to free speech and information; 
  * to fulfil a legal obligation required for processing under the law of the Union or of the Member States to which we are subject or for the performance of a task which is in the interest of public 
  * from reasons of public interest in the area of public health according to Art. 9 para. 2 lit. h and i and Art. 9 para. 3 GDPR; 
  * für archival purposes of public interest, scientific interest or historical interest. According to Art. 89 para. 1 GDPR, insofar as the right to deletion is likely to make it impossible or seriously impaired to achieve the objectives of such processing; or 
  * to assert, exercise or defend legality. 

### 9.5 RIGHT ON DATA ASSIGNMENT

You have the right to receive the personal data you have provided to us in a structured, common and machine-readable format. In addition, you have the right to have this data - without obstruction by us - answered by another person to transmit, provided that the processing is based on a consent according to Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR or Art. 9 para. 2 lit. a GDPR or on a contract gemäß Art. 6 para. 1 lit. b GDPR and processing is carried out using automated methods. 

In examination of your right to data assignment, you also have the right to have your personal data processed - without our interference - directly by to another responsible person, as far as this is technically feasible. The freedoms and rights of others will not be affected by this. 

The right to data assignment does not apply to processing of your personal data that is required to perform a task that is in public interest that has been committed to us. 

### 9.6 RIGHT OF OBJECTION

You have the right to object to the processing of your personal data at any time, which results from your special situation, on the basis of art. 6 para. 1 lit. e or lit. f GDPR; this also applies to these provisions. 

We will no longer process your personal data after your objection, unless we can prove mandatory protectable reasons to further processing of your personal data, which serves your interests, rights and freedoms, or further processing of your personal data serves to assert, exercise or defend legality. 

### 9.7 RIGHT TO REVOKE CONSENT UNDER DATA PROTECTION LAW

You have the right to revoke your data protection consent at any time. By your revocation the legality of due to your consent up to the revocation processing of your personal data will not touched.

### 9.8 RIGHT OF APPEAL

Without prejudice to any other administrative or judicial remedy, you have the right of appeal to supervisory authority, in particular in the Member State of your place of residence, of work or of the place of suspected infringement, if you believe that the processing of your personal data violates the provisions of the GDPR. The supervisory authority, to which you have lodged your complaint, will inform of the status and the results of the complaint, including the possibility of a judicial remedy under Art. 78 GDPR.

## 10\. UPDATE

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy occasionally. We will inform you in advance if major changes of privacy policy is carried out.

The use of your personal data is subject to the current version of privacy policy, which can be accessed at “Privacy Policy” on our websites. If you continue to access our website after changes has come into effect, please agree with the updated privacy policy. 

If you have any questions or comments about the above privacy policy, please do not hesitate to contact us at: 

info@ujam.com 

Version: 05/24/2017 

© 2019 NXTGN Music Technology GmbH. All rights reserved.
